A few days later
Yes, hello?
Yes, director.
Oh, I'm Lim Junbin.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Could you tell my father about it?
No, it's not anything else.
As soon as I got into the company,
I don't want the staff to be behind me when I become the director.
And I don't want to inherit the company.
Please tell your father.
No, if you tell your father, he'll understand.
I beg you.
Yes, yes.
Hello?
What's this all of a sudden?
Why isn't it working?
Wait a minute.
I'll try the speaker phone.
Hello?
It's not working all of a sudden.
I just called.
Why, why?
Where are you?
Oh, I'm just here. Why?
You didn't forget, did you?
I'm going to meet Kim Hee-yeon's daughter later.
Oh, I'm not going to go.
I'm not going to go.
Hurry up and go to the Silla Hotel Lounge in 30 minutes.
Can't you just go instead of me?
Why would I go instead of you?
I don't know why I have to go.
Hey, don't you know how helpful Kim Hee-yeon is to my father's business?
My father is my father.
I'm me.
And I'm not interested in business.
And I just have someone I love.
It's not up to you.
Go and meet her in 30 minutes.
Didn't you hear me?
Hurry up and find me and get married.
I'm with the person I love right now.
I'm with you right now.
You don't have anyone you love all of a sudden.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you in advance.
I have someone I love.
I don't want to get married because I don't want to.
That's what I know.
You're at the coffee shop you go to all the time, right?
No, it's not there. Don't think about coming.
I'm going to go now.
Wait there.
Hang up the phone.
I'm going crazy.
I think he's coming.
Oh, my God.
Why are you laughing so much?
Did I look like a child who doesn't have a job?
I'm a housewife's son.
I'm sorry, but...
I'm crying.
What?
Did something bad happen?
Did someone die?
No.
Did you go to the funeral?
Why?
Hang up the phone.
I have to go see Sunwoo.
Why?
You're lying to me that you have someone you love.
What's wrong with you?
I'm crying.
Did something get on my face?
Where is it?
What?
Honey, do you want some more?
Is it him?
Who is it?
Why can't you tell me?
Is it a lie?
No.
Don't lie to me. Let's go see Sunwoo.
Why do you want to see Sunwoo?
It's really important to you.
I'm going to tell you everything.
Don't lie to me.
What?
It's him.
Why are you so vague?
It's him?
Do you call your girlfriend?
It's him.
It's him?
His name is Lee.
What?
It's him.
His name is Lee?
It's him?
What's his name?
What?
You said you were his girlfriend.
What's his name?
It's him.
What?
Why are you sitting separately?
I'm going to fart.
What?
I'm going to fart and sit back down.
I'm next to you.
I have a friend next to me.
friend?
I'm here to introduce you to a friend.
I can't fart in here.
I have a bad stomach.
I was going to fart.
Don't lie to me.
What?
Come out to get married next month.
I'm here.
What?
I think you're uncomfortable right now.
What did you do?
We always play pranks.
What are you doing with your teeth?
Sit down.
My girlfriend is shy.
I'll sit down for a second.
Why are you putting on makeup?
Wait a minute.
I'm so scared.
I'm always funny.
What's your name?
Lee Boon
Where are you from?
I'm from Orion.
We met while playing pranks.
Are you two in love?
I'm shy.
I can't say I love you.
Are you two dating?
Why are you laughing?
Do I look handsome?
What's wrong with you?
Why are you so far away?
You're praying.
What do you like about him?
He's handsome.
I'll listen to you.
He's sexy.
Do you have a phobia?
He told me he was sexy.
You like him.
You're far away.
Thank you.
What do you like about him?
He's funny.
I like his face.
How long have you been dating?
10 years?
Be quiet.
How long have you been dating?
I don't know.
You can't speak well?
It's been a few years since I came to Korea.
I lived abroad.
I lived in Uganda.
Uganda?
Don't ask me that.
I'm not good at Korean.
What's your job?
I'm a lawyer.
I'm a farmer.
You're a farmer?
You're a farmer in Uganda?
I'm a lawyer.
Stop it.
Get out of here.
What are you going to do?
I'll talk to you.
What are you talking about?
Tell your mom and dad to come here.
What did you just say?
This is a Christian church.
Tell your mom and dad to come here.
Okay, get out of here.
Can I sit down for a while?
Why?
You're pretty.
Do you like him a lot?
Are you sure you're dating him?
How much do you like him?
As much as my head hurts.